<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.eclipse.spykit.runtime.feature"
      label="Runtime Spykit"
      version="2.0.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="ANCIT Consulting">

   <description url="http://www.ancitconsulting.com/tiki-index.php?page=eclipse-spykit">
      Almost every day we hear of new companies adopting Eclipse as
their application development platform of choice. With the number
of Eclipse Projects growing in leaps and bounds in the Eclipse
Community chances of the risk of memory bloat and performance
degradation is high.
Therefore Performance Tuning is the need of the hour in the Eclipse
Projects.
This Project is inspired by Runtime Spy, one of Core Tools available
from Eclipse.org. During our search for Runtime Spy, we realised
that the support for this tool has been stopped since Eclipse
3.2 when Eclipse was moved to OSGI.
Our motive of this project is to revive Runtime Spy back and
add more functionality into the same and also create a set of
tools that would come in handy for Performance Tuning of Eclipse
Projects.
We invite the Eclipse Community to start using the project for
their performance tuning activities. Do please log in issues
and new features that you would be interested in. We would be
more than happy to implement it and provide a release immediately.
The Project is hosted on Google Code and you may download the
latest version from eclipse-spykit.
The Source Code is also available for download thru SVN, we would
encourage the contributors to take the source and build around
it and contribute back to the project.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      [Enter Copyright Description here.]
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      [Enter License Description here.]
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Eclipse Spykit" url="https://code.google.com/a/eclipselabs.org/p/eclipse-spykit/downloads/list"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms" version="3.5.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.swt" version="3.6.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.spykit.runtime"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="2.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.spykit.runtime.snapshot"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.spykit.utils"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.spykit.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.0.qualifier"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
